Knight to queen's bishop-five.
Oh, very nice. what's leonard going to do this?
Does he give up the pawn or does he give up the position?
Let's find out.
Leonard, ready?
- Ready.  - Go.
Damn it. I slipped.
Too bad.
you know the rules of secret agent laser obstacle chess.
Leonard died again, sheldon. you're up.
Despite my deep love of chess, lasers and aerosol disinfectant,
I must forfeit.
Why?
- Because it's almost 11:00. - so?
So, penny has a "don't knock or I punch you in the throat" rule.
Hey, you know what'd be a great idea?
We get some girls over here and play laser optical strip chess.
Believe me, howard, any girl who would be willing to play that,
You don't want to see naked.
You underestimate me.
Penny. penny.
Penny.
Hey, sheldon.
It's 11:00 a.m.
I know. you're safe.
This package came while you were at work
oh, great, my rhinestones.Thank you.
- Excuse me. - what?
You have to sign this.
What is it?
When I signed for the package,
I was deputized by the united parcel service
And entrusted with its final delivery.
I now need you to acknowledge receipt of the package
So that i'm fully indemnified and no longer liable.
Sheldon, it's just a box of rhinestones.
Well, the contents are irrelevant.
A legal bailment has been created.
Is that mean nothing to you?
It means nothing to anybody.
Come here, let me show you what I'm doing.
"bailment" describes a relationship in common law
where a physical possession of personal property,
or "chattels,"
is transferred from one person, the bailor,
To another person, the bailee...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. look, look, look!
I started a business.
Obviously, not a cleaning business.
No, I'm making flower barrettes. see?
I call them penny blossoms.
I made one for myself,
then all the girls at work wanted one.
Then I showed some to this lady who runs a shop in old town.
She sells cards and homemade jewels,
She said she wanted to sell them. I said, "okay."
And in one week,i made a $156.
Good for you, Sign here.
Sheldon, don't you get it?
If this takes off,
I won't have to be a waitss anymore.
But then who will bring me my cheeseburger on tuesday nights?
Another waitress.
What's her name?
I don't know.
And you're going to let her handle my food?
Nancy. her name is nancy.
I think you're just making that up.
Sheldon, I'm sorry about your hamburger, okay?
I just don't want to be a waitress for the rest of my life.
Cheeseburger. I get a cheeseburger.
Fine, cheeseburger.
Maybe I'd be better off with nancy.
So, what do you think?
I mean, this could be a business, right?
How many of these can you make a day?
About 20.
And how much profit do you make per...Penny blossom?
I don't know, like, 50 cents. I'm not sure.
Of course you're not. all right...
Ten dollars a day times five days a week
Times 52 weeks a year is $2,600.
That's all?
Before taxes.
I don't have to pay taxes on this stuff.
I believe the internal revenue service would strongly disagree.
But, if you took advantage of modern marketing techniques,
And you optimized your manufacturing process,
You might be able to make this a viable business.
And you know about that stuff?
Penny...
I'm a physicist.
I have a working knowlge of the
Entire universe and everything it contains.
Who's radiohead?
I have a working knowledge of the important things in the universe.
Good luck.
Sheldon, hold on.
Could you maybe show me how to make more money with this.
Of course I could
Sheldon, wait!
Will you?
Just to be clear here, you're asking for my assistance.
Yes.
And you understand that will involve me telling you what to do?
I understand.
And you're not allowed to be sarcastic or snide to me while I'm doing so.
Okay.
Good.
Let's begin with the premise that
Everything you've done up to this point is wrong.
Oh, Imagine that.
Sarcasm. good-bye. No, sorry, wait. Please come back.
There. done.
All right.
12 minutes and 17 seconds. oh!
Pretty good, right?
Penny ossoms per hour.
Based on your wholesale selling price,
You'll effectively be paying yourself...
$5.19 a day.
"a day"?
There are children in a sneaker factory in indonia who outearn you.
That just can't be right.
You're questioning my math? no, sorry.
Want me to show my work?
Oh, god, no.
Just please tell me what to do about it.
All right.
Are you familiar with the development
in 1778 used interchangeable parts?
The assembly line, of course.
Okay, you know what, if I'm not allowed to be snide,
You're not allowed to be condescending.
Sthat wasn't a part of our original agreement,
And I don't agree to it now.
L right, fine.
How are we supposed to set up machines and conveyor belts in my apartment?
You're thinking of the moving assembly line,
An understandable but not excusable mistake. no.
The moving assembly line, that was introduced by henry ford in 1908.
That innovation is what made possible our modern consumer
Culture by enabling a low-unit cost for manufactured goods.
I guess that isn' one of the topics discussed on your radiohead.
Let's go. we're going to miss the coming attractions.
What's the matter?
I think I bruised a testicle capturing that last pawn.
* Give me some timeon ato blow the man down *
* I'm a deepwatesailor just come fromong Kong *
* Give me way, hey, blow the man down *
* If you give me some whiskey *
* I'll sing you a song *
* Give me some time to blow the man down. *
Hello?
Hello. Hello.
* Come quickly lay aft
* To the break of the poop *
* To me way, hey, blow the man down *
* Or I'll help you along with the toe of my boot *
* Give me some me to blow the man down.
W-W-Wait, what's going on?
I assume you're referring to the sea chanty.
It's a rhythmic work song
designedo increase productivity.
Yeah, it's crazy, but it totally works.
Look, we made is Penny Blossom
in under three minutes.
Terrific, but that kind of raises more questions than it answers.
Penny's making hair accessories.
I'm helping her optimize her manufacturing process.
Alright, break's over.
* Pay attention to orders now you one and all... *
Hold on. What are you using as a bonding agent?
Hot glue.
You're kidding.
Any of the cnoacrylates would do a better job.
It won't work, the flower'too porous.
What if we infused the bottom layer
with silicone-RTV to provide a better mounting surface?
Intriguing.
Good question.
Wh are your marketing and distribution channels?
Well, ere are the waitresses at my work,
and this cute, little shop in Old Town...
Hush, hush, hush, hush, hush-- virtually non-existent.
I'm thinking that we set her up
with a hosted turnkey e-commerce system to start.
Why not eliminate the middle man?
We could install a small server farm
with a static IP in her bedroom.
She'd need some kind of industrial cooling system.
Of course, but before we set up
a marketing andistribution infrastructure,
we should finish optimizing the manufacturing process.
To start with, she has a terrible problem
with moisture-induced glitter clump.
Yeah, it's a bitch.
Uh, I've seen this before.
Where?
It's a common stripper problem.
They dance, they swe, they clump.
Are you thinking about adding
a desiccant ke calcium sulfate?
Actually, I'm thinking about this one stripper named Vega.
But re, calcium sulfate could work.
Let's think out the box for a moment.
How about a molecular sieve?
I've got a spaghetti strainer in the kitchen.
Hey, we could liberate some
micro-porous charcoal from the chem lab.
Oh, great.Raj, why don't you and Howard go get the charcoal?
Leonard, why don't you start working on preliminary web site designs.
I'll make some space in our apartment
so we can move the manufacturing process.
Well, what's wrong with my apartment?
It's not my apartment.
Wait, wait, what am I going to do?
Uh, hey, it's your business.
Do whatever you want
Okay, cool.
I'm gonna take a nap.
I'm still twinking things a little bit,
but this will give you the general idea of the Web site.
So, what do you guys think?
Uh, pretty much any way I say that
is going to hurt his feelings.
Okay, what's wrong with it?
What's wrong with it?
Not you. I wasn't asking you.
Penny?
Uh, well, it's a little juvenile.
I mean, it kind of looks like the MySpace page
of a 13-year-old girl.
No, it doesn't.
Please. Dateline could use it to attract predators.
Penny, this is your enterprise,
so it's ultimately your decision,
but based on the quality of his work,
I'd strongly recommend that we let Leonard go.
You want to fire me?
What I want is irrelevant. This is Penny's decision.
Penny?
Excuse me, but if I did such a bad job,
then why do we already have orders?
We do?
Uh-huh. Look.
Mrs. Fiona Fondell from Huntsville, Alabama has ordered two.
No kidding. Two? Uh-huh
Look at the comments.
Thank you, Penny Blossoms. These will be perfect, to cover my bald spot."
that is so sweet.
Camouflaging bald spots.
That's primarily a male concern.
Perhaps could expand our market.
How are flower barrettes going to appeal to men?
We add Bluetooth!
Brilliant. Men love Bluetooth.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
you want to make a hair barrette with Bluetooth?
Penny, everything is better with Bluetooth.
Holy crap.
Someone just ordered a thousand Penny Blossoms.
Get out!
Who needs a thousand sparkly flower barrettes
with rhinestones?
"The Fifth Annual East Rutherford, New Jersey,
Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Alliance Luau."
Oh, another market to expand
To balding gay men.
And I'll bet lesbians love Bluetooth.
We should get to work.
Wait, wait, why does it say "one-day rush"?
Since when do we offer a one-day rush?
Amazon offers one-day rush.
Yeah, but they don't have to glue the books together.
How the hell are we going to make
a thousand Penny Blossoms in one day?
Don't yell at me.
I'm not manufacturing. I'm just Web design.
Okay, well, I'm gonna have to call and cancel the order.
Excuse me,
but was this not your goal?
Financial independence
through entrepreneurial brilliance and innovation?
My brilliance and innovation, of course, but still.
I just don't see how we can pull this off.
That, right there, that equivotion and self-doubt,
that is not the American spirit.
Did Davy Crockett quit at the Alamo?
Did Jim Bowie?
They didn't quit.They were massacred...
by like a gazillion angry Mexicans.
Let me put it this way.
Your gross receipts on this one order
will be over $3,000 for one night's work.
You guys get started.
What are you doing?
Going online to buy shoes!
* She'll be coming round the mountain when she comes * * When she comes
* She'll be coming round the mountain * * when she comes *
* When she comes *
* She'll be coming round the mountain *
* She'll be coming round the mountain... *
You know, if I wand to spend my Saturday nights doing this,
I could have stayed in India.
Oh, stop with the fake third world crap.
Your father's a gynecologist.
And you had a use full of servants.
We only had four servants.
And two of them were children.
How we doing?
We have 128 assorted Penny Blossoms ready to ship.
Oh, God, we're never gonna finish in time.
* When she comes * When she comes
Wait, hold.Who made Sheldon the boss anyway?
I believe I'm hearing some negativity on the factor floor.
So
Penny, the labor force is a living organism
that must be carefully nurtured.
Any counterproductive grumbling must be skillfully
headed off by management. Observe
Hey!
Less talk, more work!
Nicely done.
Thank you.
You hear any union talk, you let know.
* Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah... *
* Someone's in the kitchen I know-ow-ow-ow *
* Someone's in the kihen with Dinah... *
Sheldon?
Sheldon!
* 'Cause I sold my soul to the company store. *
Honey, do you want some coffee?
I don't drink coffee.
Come on, but if you don't stay awake
we'll never finish in time.
I'm sorry, coffee's out of the question.
When I moved to California,
I promised my mother that I wouldn't start doing drugs.
Leonard, help.
Sheldon, we still have 380 of these things to make
I have complete faith that you will make them.Good night.
Leonard?!
But, Sheldon,without your insight and leadership
this entire enterprise will surely fail.
You're right, of course.
Here, this will help.
Very well,
but if this leads to opiates or hallucinogenics,
You're going to have to answer to my mother.
Look at Planck's Constant.
It could not be less arbitrary.
If it varied slightly, life as we know would not exist.Bang!
Now, now, let's reconsider the entire argument,
but with entropy reversed and effect peceding cause.
So you are thinking a universe
that's not expanding from the center--
no, it is retreating from a, from a possibility space. Bang!
This is a space where we are all essentially Alice
through the looking glass,
standing in front of the Red Queen,
and we're being offered a cracker to quench our thirst. Bang!
Of course, in another universe, let's call it universe prime,
there's another Sheldon
We should let him go to bed. Bang!
I can't believe we actually did it.
1,000 friggin' Penny Blossoms.
I just want you guys to know
I am really grateful for your help.
And for ever dollar I make, I'm gog to give you 20 cents.
That's your entire profit margin.
Oh.Then never mind.
I'll print out the shipping label.
What?
We got an e-mail from the East Rutherford, New Jersey,
Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender liance.
They want another thousand Penny Blossoms.
Really?
One-day rush.
I really need to take that off the Web site.
Okay, well, guess we'd better get started.
You can't be serious.
Come on.
What about the living organism of the workforce
and the American spirit?!
And Jiminy Crockett at the Alamo?!
Davy Crockett.
Jiminy Crockett was cricket.
yes, yes, I know that, okay?
I'm tired-- I've had like 18 cups of coffee.
The point is, if we just pull together, we can do this.
Who's with me?
Penny, although you may find it hard to believe,
We do have lives.
Leonard?
Sorry.
My apologies to the gay community
of East Rutherford, New Jersey.
Where's the coffee?!
We're all out.
No problem.
I'll be back before this banana hits the ground.
Yes!
Sorry, guys, but Secret Agent Laser Obstacle Lunch is just stupid.